Class of 1889 Records, 1868, 1880-1954, 1982-83, 1998
Smith College Archives
Class of 1889 Records
1868, 1880-1954, 1982-83, 1998
Smith College. Class of 1889.
RG 80 UUID:772ec7a2-75ec-4487-be2d-636fc1372acb
4 boxes (1 linear ft. and 8 linear inches)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, letters, publications, course notes, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1889.
The Class of 1889 was the eleventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1889 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1889. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, publications, course notes, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1889.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1889 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1889: Baccalaureate Service 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 1)
- Class of 1889: Commencement 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 2)
- Class of 1889: Commencement Music 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 3)
- Class of 1889: Farewell Party 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 4)
- Class of 1889: Groups 1885-89 (Box 1447, Folder 5)
- Class of 1889: History 1889, undated (Box 1447, Folder 6)
- Class of 1889: Ivy Day 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 7)
- Class of 1889: Junior Prom 1888 (Box 1447, Folder 8)
- Class of 1889: Class Letters 1890, 1919-20, 1930, 1932-35 (Box 1447, Folder 9)
- Class of 1889: Organization 1885-1929 (Box 1447, Folder 10)
- Class of 1889: Class Photo Book 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 11)
- Class of 1889: Reunions 1890 (Box 1447, Folder 12)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs undated (Box 1447, Folder 13)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1914 (Box 1447, Folder 14)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1919 (Box 1447, Folder 15)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1924 (Box 1447, Folder 16)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1934 (Box 1447, Folder 17)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1939 (Box 1447, Folder 18)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1949 (Box 1447, Folder 19)
- Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs 1954 (Box 1447, Folder 20)
- Class of 1889: Songs undated (Box 1447, Folder 21)
- Class of 1889: Sophomore Reception 1886 (Box 1447, Folder 22)
- Class of 1889: Class Supper 1889 (Box 1447, Folder 23)
- Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics 1889 (Box 1448, Folder 1)
- Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics ("Electra" Manuscript Book) 1889 (Box 1448, Folder 2)
- Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) 1889 (Box 1448, Folder 3)
- Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) 1889 (Box 1448, Folder 4)
- Class of 1889: Composite 1889 (Box 1449, Folder 1)
- Class of 1889: Abbot, Ella Caroline (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1449, Folder 2)
- Class of 1889: Allen, Lucy Ellis (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1449, Folder 3)
- Class of 1889: Atwater, Elsie Welling (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 4)
- Class of 1889: Blake, Jennie Maria 1886, undated (Box 1449, Folder 5)
- Class of 1889: Blinn, Harriet Louise undated (Box 1449, Folder 6)
- Class of 1889: Blodgett, Grace Allen undated (Box 1449, Folder 7)
- Class of 1889: Buell, Gertrude Frances undated (Box 1449, Folder 8)
- Class of 1889: Buswell, Alice Maud (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 9)
- Class of 1889: Carr, Agnes (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 10)
- Class of 1889: Cobb, Harriet Redfield (Box 1449, Folder 11)
- Class of 1889: Colgan, Mary Ella (Photographs, etc) 1889, 1914 (Box 1449, Folder 12)
- Class of 1889: Cullinan, Catherine (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 13)
- Class of 1889: Cushing, Jane Delia (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 14)
- Class of 1889: Davis, Grace Gilbert undated (Box 1449, Folder 15)
- Class of 1889: Deane, Harriet Robinson undated (Box 1449, Folder 16)
- Class of 1889: Dickinson, Martha Gilbert 1892, 1898, 1900-01, 1908-10, 1915 (Box 1449, Folder 17)
- Class of 1889: Doane, Caroline Ida (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 18)
- Class of 1889: Fiske, Ida Mabel undated (Box 1449, Folder 19)
- Class of 1889: Fletcher, Mabel (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 20)
- Class of 1889: Gale, Anna (Photographs, etc) 1886-87, 1890, undated (Box 1449, Folder 21)
- Class of 1889: Gaylord, Mary Foster (Photographs) 1889, undated (Box 1449, Folder 22)
- Class of 1889: Gere, Mary Elizabeth undated (Box 1449, Folder 23)
- Class of 1889: Gilmour, Anna Catherine (Photographs) 1889, undated (Box 1449, Folder 24)
- Class of 1889: Goodwin, May Amelia (Photographs, etc) 1889-92, 1896, 1898, 1900, 1903, undated (Box 1449, Folder 25)
- Class of 1889: Gray, Nellie undated (Box 1449, Folder 26)
- Class of 1889: Hastings, Caroline Ella undated (Box 1449, Folder 27)
- Class of 1889: Hazen, Emily (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 28)
- Class of 1889: Hopkins, Martha Austin (Photographs, etc) 1885-87, 1889, undated (Box 1449, Folder 29)
- Class of 1889: Johnson, Alice Robinson (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 30)
- Class of 1889: Johnson, Alice Robbins undated (Box 1449, Folder 31)
- Class of 1889: Knowles, Jane Sherrill (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 32)
- Class of 1889: Lovejoy, Margaret Waldo 1922, 1982, 1998, undated (Box 1449, Folder 33)
- Class of 1889: Loveland, Helen Isabella undated (Box 1449, Folder 34)
- Class of 1889: Mason, Mary Arlina (Photographs) 1902, undated (Box 1449, Folder 35)
- Class of 1889: Moore, Julia Harrison (Photographs) undated (Box 1449, Folder 36)
- Class of 1889: Newland, Sarah Luella (Photographs) 1889, undated (Box 1450, Folder 1)
- Class of 1889: Paine, Elizabeth Elmore (Photographs, etc) 1868, 1884-89, 1891, 1925, undated (Box 1450, Folder 2)
- Class of 1889: Parker, Harriet Eliza 1896, 1908-09, 1913, 1930, 1932, 1934-42, 1945-47 (Box 1450, Folder 3)
- Class of 1889: Peirce, Eliza Metcalf undated (Box 1450, Folder 4)
- Class of 1889: Read, Marion Pugh 1914-15, 1921 (Box 1450, Folder 5)
- Class of 1889: Reed, Theodora Williams undated (Box 1450, Folder 6)
- Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy 1885-87, 1893, undated (Box 1450, Folder 7)
- Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy (Course notes, Bible) 1888 (Box 1450, Folder 8)
- Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy (Course notes, Bible) 1885 (Box 1450, Folder 9)
- Class of 1889: Robinson, Harriet Marcia 1889 (Box 1450, Folder 10)
- Class of 1889: Scribner, Eleanor undated (Box 1450, Folder 11)
- Class of 1889: Seaver, Florence White (Photographs, etc) 1886-87, 1889, 1893, 1947, undated (Box 1450, Folder 12)
- Class of 1889: Sebring, Emma Goodeve 1923, 1925, 1983 (Box 1450, Folder 13)
- Class of 1889: Seelye, Abigail Taylor 1895, undated (Box 1450, Folder 14)
- Class of 1889: Seelye, Anna Hawley 1896, undated (Box 1450, Folder 15)
- Class of 1889: Shepard, Anna North (Photographs) 1888 (Box 1450, Folder 16)
- Class of 1889: Swan, Almira French undated (Box 1450, Folder 17)
- Class of 1889: Symmes, Frances Newton 1888, 1890, undated (Box 1450, Folder 18)
- Class of 1889: Taylor, Alice Stanley (Photographs) 1888, undated (Box 1450, Folder 19)
- Class of 1889: Taylor, Elizabeth Davenport 1887 (Box 1450, Folder 20)
- Class of 1889: Thayer, Mary S. undated (Box 1450, Folder 21)
- Class of 1889: Thompson, Annie Maynard 1935 (Box 1450, Folder 22)
- Class of 1889: Tilton, Mary Susan (Photographs) undated (Box 1450, Folder 23)
- Class of 1889: Trow, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1450, Folder 24)
- Class of 1889: Washburn, Mary Nightingale (Photographs) undated (Box 1450, Folder 25)
- Class of 1889: Washburn, Mary N. (Sketch book) 1880 (Box 1450, Folder 26)
- Class of 1889: White, Grace Grosvenor 1918, 1925, undated (Box 1450, Folder 27)
- Class of 1889: Whitfield, Inez Harrington (Photographs, etc) 1929, undated (Box 1450, Folder 28)